YUEN Sing Chun (Calvin)

Frontend Developer

ABOUT ME

Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience in building web and mobile app using React, React Native, and Typescript. A team player with a strong ability to collaborate with cross-functional teams and effectively communicate technical concepts.

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Hong Kong
- scyuenab@gmail.com
- (852) 5168 7161
- https://portfolio-calvin-yuen.ve rcel.app
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sing-chun-yuen-423a09185/

EXPERIENCE

App Bar

FRONTEND ENGINEER

Oct 2022 - Jan 2024

- Actively engaged in the development of numerous features for the mobile app "A.Life" by React Native
- Developed and implemented multiple features for the "HUMA by AXA" mobile app using React Native.
- Build the CMS of the "A.Life" and "HUMA by AXA" by Next.js
- Talkbox Limited

WEB DEVELOPER

Aug 2021 - Aug 2022

- Built the tenant management website of Airside from scratch, ranging from project bootstrap to every specific features like e-directory, tenant service applications and so on.
- Developed plenty of features for the school management console named "Compus"

EDUCATION

The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING 2017-2021 WITH FIRST CLASS HONOR

CERTIFICATION

- AWS Certified Solution Architect Associate (2023 JAN)
- JLPT N3 (2021 JUL)

SKILLS

React Native	React	Typesciprt
Next.js	Redux	Git
AWS Solution Architect	NestIS	

LANGUAGES

English	Mandarin	Cantonese (Native)
Japanese (JLPT N3)		